

Turkev.Istanbul

🛮 (+90)5411027785 | 🔀 mahtaaaghajani@gmail.com | 🔏 ahead-lake.surge.sh | 🛅 mahta-aghajani

Summary_

A UI/UX designer with 5 years of experience, and a background in food delivery systems, online airplane ticket booking, E-Commerce, and Installment Payment. By understanding front-end development, I am able to create designs that are not only visually appealing but also technically feasible.

Skills

 Hueristic Evaluation
 Affinity Diagram
 Competitors Benchmark
 Information Architecture
 Journey Mapping
 Figma

 Figjam
 Adobe XD
 Illustrator
 Photoshop
 HTML
 CSS
 Jquery

Work Experience

WorldsUnited States, Remote

UI DESIGNER Feb. 2023 - July. 2023

- · Promoted user interfaces by creating wireframes and mockups delivering attractive, user-friendly and unique website.
- Building a robust and comprehensive Chakra Design System for ensuring consistent and cohesive designs across all projects, enabling team to
 maintain a unified visual language and user experience.
- By leveraging the capabilities of Webflow and Softr automation tools, Creating Interaction Websites.

Freelancer Dubai,Remote

UI-UX DESIGNER Nov. 2022 - Feb. 2023

- · Brainstormed with peers and other members of design team to determine enhancements and product features
- Managed 2 projects effectively in demanding environment with tight deadlines
- Documented each step in product's design process for use in manuals
- Suggested enhancements to product design that would improve user experience
- Developed Skills Like Heuristic Evaluation, User Flows, Competitor Benchmark, High-Fi and Low-Fi Wireframes, user stories, Journey Mapping, Personas

Mealzo United Kingdom, Remote

UI-UX DESIGNER

No. 2020 - June. 2022

- Designed User Interface for websites and communicate with front-end developers to deliver HTML and CSS friendly designs, Designed Word-Press based websites and managed the contents, Created User Interface for almost +10 Wordpress Websites
- Collaborated with stakeholders and marketing team to identify user and business requirements Designed mobile and web app for multiple types of devices and created responsive layout and UI components
- · Responsible for UX Design process, including Competitive Benchmarks ,Information Architecture, Wire framing and Prototyping
- Worked on 5 Projects: Food Delivery Platform, Financial Management Application, Tracking Application for Drivers to Assign or Accept Orders for Delivery, IT Solution Website (I Also Convert it to HTML/CSS)

Cowsel Company Baku, Azerbaijan, Remote

UI-UX DESIGNER

Feb.2020 - July.2020

- Redesigned User Interface for ERP System
- Collaborated with +10 Team Members in Agile Team
- Created Visual Assets for Company and Social Media Channels: Instagram, Youtube, Facebook
- Designed Landing Pages for 2 Projects :online shop, Sim Card Selling Website

Fara System Fartak Tabriz, Iran

FRONT-END DEVELOPER Dec. 2018 - Jan. 2020

- Designed and Developed User Interfaces for almost +5 Travel Agency Websites System with HTML/CSS /Jquery
- Created Website for University Website With HTML//CSS/Jquery
- Converted 1 onlineshop from adobe XD to live code with Pure HTML,CSS
- · Worked On 3 Types of Projects: Travel Agencies, University Website, Online Shop Ecommerce Website

Certificates

- Jun 2022 Visual Design, Interaction Design Foundation
- Jan 2022 **Conducting Usability Testing**, Interaction Design Foundation
- Jan 2022 **Become a Ux Designer From Scratch**, Interaction Design Foundation
- Jan 2022 **Journey Mapping,** Interaction Design Foundation
- Jan 2022 **User Experience Design**, Interaction Design Foundation

Education

Shahid Madani University

Tabriz,Iran

BACHELOR DEGREE Mar. 2014 - Mar. 2018

• Software Engineering (Information Technology)